-Hey, guys.. -Wait! Let me tell them.
-嘿，夥計們… -等等，我來跟他們講。
-Sure. -Joey's gonna be..
-好 -喬伊要...
a celebrity guest on a game show.
在一個益智節目中做嘉賓了。
Really? Which one?
真的？哪個節目？
Fish. Seaweed.
魚，海草
-A sunken ship. -Things you find in the ocean.
-沉船… -海中之物…
-You're gonna be on Pyramid! -Yeah.
-你要上智力金字塔! -對
-That was our favorite game show ever. -Except for Match Game.
-哦，那是我們最喜歡的益智節目了! -除了匹配賽以外!
Or Win, Lose or Draw.
還有輸贏簽。
What did I marry into?
瞧瞧我結的親家。
You guys wanna come and watch me tape the show?
你們想明天來看我錄節目嗎？
Oh, we can't. We're throwing Phoebe a bachelorette party.
不行，我們要給菲比開個婚前告別單身狂歡。
Yeah. Sorry, boys, this ride's closing.
對嘍，抱歉，兄弟們，此路不通。
And Chandler and I have this stupid college alumni thing.
哦，錢勒和我要參加一個校友聚會。
I can't believe you get to meet Donny Osmond.
難以置信你要跟多尼·奧斯蒙德做節目。
Seriously?
當真？
Ross and I always wanted to be Donny and Marie.
羅斯和我以前總想學多尼和馬瑞一樣。
You guys just keep getting cooler and cooler.
你們倆還越說越起勁兒了。
Yeah, we used to perform for our family and friends.
對，我們以前還在家裡和朋友面前表演過勒。
Oh, God, that's right. I blocked that out.
哦，沒錯，我還真把它給忘了。
I'm leaving you.
我要離開你了。
The One Where The Stripper Cries
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
It's so weird to see all these people again.
又見到這些人了。
Oh, my God, look. There's Jeffrey Klarik.
哦，我的上帝，那是傑佛.克拉瑞。
-Who? -He was roommates with John Rosoff.
-誰? -約翰.盧瑟夫的室友。
He went out with Andrea Tamborino.
他當時跟安卓.特布裡諾拍拖。
She dumped him for Michael Skloff.
她後來又跟麥克.斯克勞夫好上了。
Did I go to this school?
我上的是這所學校嗎？
Hey, there's Missy Goldberg. You gotta remember her.
嘿，那是米西.戈爾伯格，你肯定記得她。
Sure. Nice.
當然，她很正點。
Dude, you're married to my sister.
哥們兒，你可跟我老妹結了婚的。
You're right. By saying "nice, " I'm virtually licking her.
你說的沒錯，我誇她正點就是跟她不正經了？
Hey, I hear she's single again. You think I should ask her out?
嘿，我聽說她又單身了 你說我是不是該跟她約會呢？
Are you asking permission to break the pact?
你是不是想要打破君子協定？
Yes, please.
對了，求求你。
Hey. Hey, check out the fliers for the band.
瞧瞧樂隊的傳單。
-I made them on a Macintosh. -Awesome.
-我在機房的蘋果機上做的。 -乖乖
The name really stands out.
名字還挺醒目的。
Thanks to a little something called Helvetica Bold 24-point.
這多虧有了24針Helvetic打印機。
Man, we're gonna rock that Asian Student Union.
哥們兒，我們要在"亞學聯"蓋了。
-Hey, guys. -Hey, Missy.
-嘿，夥計們。 -嘿，米西。
-Our band is playing on Friday. -Yeah, you should come check us out.
-你知道嗎，我們樂隊星期五演出。 -是啊，你該來看看。
We're called Way/No Way.
我們管它叫"行，還是不行"。
-No way. -Way.
-不行。 -行!
-Great. I'll be there. -Fresh.
-好吧，到時見 -新鮮
-Boss. -Mint.
-老闆. -薄荷.
-She's gone. -I know it.
-她走了。 -我知道。
-I am totally gonna ask her out. -Dude, I was gonna ask her out.
-你知道嗎，我一定要約到她。 -哥們兒，我還想約她呢。
-I said it first, bro. -Well, I thought it first, Homes.
-是我先說的，兄弟。 -那我還先想到的呢，老哥。
-Look, if you date.. -Wait! Wait! What are we doing?
-聽著，你要是約… -等等，我們在幹嗎呢？
What we have is too important to mess it up over some girl.
我們倆可不能重色輕友反目成仇
I mean, we can get laid any time we want.
再說，天涯何處無芳草。
Totally.
就是。
-I had sex in high school. -Me too. I'm good at it.
-我高中就有性生活了。 -我也是，我是情場高手。
All right, I say we make a pact.
好吧，我們倆立個君子協定，
Neither of us will go out with Missy Goldberg.
誰都不許跟米西.戈爾伯格約會。
You got it.
一言為定。
That's Missy Goldberg, Phoebe Cates and Molly Ringwald..
那麼，現在我們就不能跟米西.戈爾伯格 菲比.凱特
-who we can't go out with. -Those are the pacts.
-還有莫莉.裡沃特約會了 -沒錯，約法三章。
And Sheena Easton. But we probably couldn't get her anyway.
哦，還有西娜.伊斯特 反正我們也追不上她。
Maybe not you.
你追不上她倒是真的。
Well, I officially give you permission to break the pact.
好吧，我正式授權允許你打破君子協定。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Here I go. Hey, remember how scary it used to be going up to girls in college?
好，我要上啦。 嘿，還記得上學時你跟女孩說話都慌神嗎？
-Your hands are shaking. -I know. And I can't stop sweating.
-你的手在發抖呢。 -我知道，我還一個勁地冒汗。
Five, four, three. Applause.
5，4，3，鼓掌。
Yeah!
哦!
Welcome. It is Soap Opera Week here on Pyramid.
歡迎大家，這裡是智力金字塔，肥皂劇之周。
Let's meet our contestants. First, Gene Lester is a database specialist.
來看看選手們 首先，是數據庫專家金.拉斯特。
He's gonna be playing with Days of Our Lives star Joey Tribbiani.
他的搭檔是「我們的日子」 劇中的明星 喬伊-崔比阿尼
And over here, we have Henrietta Cherry.
這位是Henrietta Cherry.
I know it can be intimidating for regular people to be around celebrities..
嘿，我知道普通人跟名人在一起時都會緊張。
but relax. I'm just like you, only better-looking and richer.
不過沒事兒，我跟你差不多 就是好看點兒，錢多點兒。
She'll be playing with star of General Hospital, Leslie Charleson.
…她要跟"綜合醫院" 劇中的明星萊絲莉.查爾森搭檔。
Welcome, everybody. Good luck to all of you. Let's play Pyramid.
歡迎大家，祝各位好運。 我們開始玩智力金字塔，好嗎？
All right? Now, we flipped a coin before the show.
我們在節目開始之前已經拋過硬幣了。
Gene, you won the toss, so you'll start. Which category?
金，你猜對硬幣，所以你先開始。
-"You Crossed the Line." -"You Crossed the Line." Joey..
-你選那組題目？ -我選"You Cross The Line"。
describe for Gene these things that have lines.
喬伊，你給金描述那些有線條的東西。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please. Ready? Go.
限時20秒。 預備，開始。
Okay, it's a store like a supermarket.
呃，像超市一樣的商店…哦！
I see what I did there. Okay, okay. I'm writing in my..
我明白，我明白。 呃，我寫…
-Diary. -No, more like a notebook.
-日記。 -不是，更像個筆記本…該死！
If I'm building a house, the plan..
哦，要是我建所房子
isn't called a "shmooprint"..
那個規劃，不是叫平面圖的…
I can't do that either?
帶個圖字都不行？
In high school, I once had sex with a girl right in the middle of the..?
在高中，有一次我跟個女孩在…
-Cafeteria? -Yeah, but they're not looking for that.
-校食堂。 -是有過那麼一次，但那不是他們要的那個詞
-Thank you so much for this. -You like it?
-你們辦的還真不錯。 -哦，你喜歡嗎？
Oh, my God, it's all so elegant.
哦，我的上帝，還挺高雅的呢。
When's the dirty stuff starting?
什麼時候開始來點兒刺激的？
-What? -The strippers and the guys dancing..
-什麼？ -你知道的，脫衣舞男啦
and, you know, pee-pees flying about.
男子艷舞啦，PP晃來晃去之類的。
Phoebe, I.. There isn't gonna be any "flying about."
菲比，我… 今天沒有艷舞表演。
We thought we were a little too mature for stuff like that.
事實上，我們覺得我們老大不小的了 還玩這些？
Oh, okay.
哦，好吧。
I see what you're doing. That's fine. This is all there is. Just tea. Okay.
我知道你們在幹嗎，好的。 今天就是個茶話會，好的。
Raunchy.
嘸，真髒啊。
Seriously, Phoebe, it's not gonna be that kind of a party.
真的，菲比，這不是那種狂歡。
Really? So this is..?
真的？這就是
This is my big sendoff into married life?
我的婚前單身告別會？
Rachel, this is the only bachelorette party I'm ever gonna have.
瑞秋，我可就只有這一次單身告別會啊。
I've got a big wad of ones in my purse.
我提包裡可有一大筐的酒呢。
Really? I mean, really? It's just tea?
真的？今天就只是茶話會？
No.
當然不是了。
-Phoebe, of course there's more. -Okay.
-菲比，還有別的呢。 -好吧
I mean, let me just go talk to Monica..
我是說，我去問問莫妮卡
and get an ETA on the pee-pees.
看什麼時候上PP艷舞。
We've got a problem.
我們有點問題
Oh, my God. Did someone find my Band-Aid in their scone?
哦, 天啊! 有誰發現我的橡皮膏在他們的烤餅裡了嗎?
That wasn't an apricot?
那不是一個杏仁嗎?
-What's the problem? -Okay. Phoebe wants a stripper.
-什麼問題? 菲比想要脫衣舞男
I thought we said we were too grown up for that.
我記得我說過 我們長大了, 不需要那個了
Yeah, well, it's what she wants.
對, 但是她想要的
Hey, why is the page that has strippers on it dog-eared?
嘿, 為什麼有脫衣舞男電話的一頁折上了?
Chandler was in Tulsa. I was bored.
錢德在Tulsa. 我太無聊了
Please don't tell him.
請別告訴他
Now, Gene, I must remind you, you need all six of these to stay in the game.
現在, 金, 我要提醒你 必須答對全部6題才能留下來
Describe for Joey "things you find in your refrigerator."
給喬伊描述冰箱裡的物品。
They might as well just give us the points.
我看這簡直是給我們送分啊。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock. Ready? Go.
限時20秒。預備，開始。
-You put this in your coffee. -A spoon. Your hands. Your face.
-你往咖啡裡加的東西。 -勺子，手，臉。
-It's white. -Paper. Snow. A ghost!
-它是白色的。 -紙，雪，鬼！
-It's heavier than milk. -A rock. A dog. The Earth.
-它比牛奶重。 -呃，石頭，狗，地球。
Pass.
過。
-You put it on a sandwich. -Salami. Anchovies. Jam.
-你往三明治上放的東西。 -薩拉米香腸，鳳尾魚，果醬。
-It's white. -Paper. Snow. A ghost!
-白色的。 -紙，雪，鬼！
-It's made from eggs. -Chickens?
-它使用雞蛋做的。 -小雞？
Pass.
過
-You put this on a hamburger. -Ketchup! Relish!
-你往漢堡包上放的東西。 -番茄醬。
Stop!
停。
Oh, time's up. Well, Joey, you were..
哦，時間到。 喬伊，你…
almost on a roll there. Gene..
差點兒就上榜了。金..
you'll have a chance to go to the Winner's Circle, but now..
你下半場還可能有機會進入決勝圈的。 但是現在...
Henrietta, you're going to the Winner's Circle to try your luck for $10,000..
亨瑞達 你待會兒將進入決勝圈一試運氣贏取$10000。
right after this. Don't go away.
不要走開。
And we're out.
我們出局了
-How about that ketchup thing, huh? -Yeah. Impressive.
-剛才的番茄醬怎麼樣啊? -對!印象深刻
Oh, so we didn't win. But it's fun to play the game, right?
哦，我們沒贏，不過樂在其中也不錯，對吧？
I got a kid starting college. I have to get surgery on my knee.
我有個孩子剛上大學，我的膝蓋要做手術
You just lost me 10 grand.
你剛剛讓我損失一萬美金。
Oh, wow.
喔。
I'm so sorry. Okay, I promise, we'll do better next time.
抱歉，我保證下一輪我們發揮好一點。
Well, I will, because I won't be playing with you.
我會發揮好一些，因為我不會跟你搭檔了。
Hey, some of those are pretty hard.
你要知道，有些題目也太難了點。
Like, why would there be a ghost in my fridge?
例如我的冰箱裡怎麼會有鬼的？
Yeah.
是啊
-So Saturday night? -I'd love to.
-那麼，星期六晚上。 -我很願意。
Great.
太好了。
So how come it took you so long to ask me out?
你怎麼這麼長時間才約我？
Oh, well, this is gonna sound kind of silly..
呃，這聽起來有些愚蠢，但是…
but do you remember my roommate, Chandler Bing?
你還記得我的室友 錢德-賓？
Sure. He was in your "band."
當然，他在你的"樂隊"裡。
It's been 16 years, but the air quotes still hurt.
已經16年了，不過那個引號還是挺傷人的。
-Sorry. -That's okay. Anyway..
-對不起。 -沒關係。
Well, he and I both really liked you a lot..
呃，總之，我們那時都很喜歡你，
but we didn't want it to jeopardize our friendship, so we made a pact..
但是我們又不想為此傷友誼 所以我們約定
that neither of us could ask you out.
誰也不能跟你約會。
-Really? -Yeah, why?
-真的？ -是啊，怎麼了？
Well, Chandler and I used to make out.
呃，錢德和我經常一塊兒親熱。
A lot.
經常
-You did? -Yeah.
-你們倆？ -對呀
-We'd go to the science lab after-hours. -And on my turf?!
-我們常在下課後到實驗室去。 -還在我的地盤上？
Hey, where is this guy? It's been over an hour.
嘿，那傢伙還沒來？都一個多小時了。
He's coming from Jersey. He said he'd get here as fast as he could.
他要從Jersey趕過來，他說會盡快趕到的。
Oh, by the way, Phoebe's friend Marge found an earring in cucumber sandwich.
哦, 對了, 菲比的朋友馬切 在黃瓜三文治中發現了一隻耳環
Well, it's not mi..
呃.........它不是我的..
I am not on my game today.
我今天沒有玩遊戲
-Who is it? -It's the police.
-誰呀？ -警察。
The police!
哦，警察！
That's right. It's Officer Goodbody.
沒錯，是"好身材"警官。
What's the matter, officer? Has someone been bad?
出什麼事啦，警官？是不是有人調皮了？
That's a lot of stairs.
唔，這麼多樓梯。
Boy.
唔，老天！
You should warn people there's no elevator.
你們應該告訴人家這棟樓沒電梯。
I should not have had that Mexican food for lunch.
我午飯不該吃墨西哥菜。
Are you gonna be okay, Officer..?
你沒事吧，警官…
-Goodbody. -If you say so.
-"好身材" -你非要那麼說的話。
So where's the young lady..
那麼，哪位是
who I am supposed to take downtown?
我要「逮捕」的年輕女士啊？
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
You, my dear, are under arrest.
你, 親愛的, 被捕啦!!!(不許動)
Cardiac arrest?
心博停止了?
All right. Somebody show me where to plug in my box..
好了，誰告訴我插座在哪
and we'll get this party started.
我們開始狂歡吧。
-Over here? -Yeah.
-在這? -對啊!
-All right. -Rachel?
-好吧 -瑞秋？
-Yeah? -Are you kidding?
-啊？ -呃，你是不是在開我的玩笑？
We didn't know you wanted a stripper, so we got the phone book..
好吧，我們原來不知道你想要脫衣舞男 所以...
-and got the first name we could find. -How old's your phone book?
-我們臨時在電話簿上找了一個。 -你們的電話簿有多老了？
Oh, my God, this man is gonna get naked in my apartment.
哦，我的上帝 這個男人要在我的公寓裡脫光光！
God, no. I don't wanna see him take his clothes off.
哦，上帝，不要。我可不想看他跳脫衣舞。
Are you talking about me?
你們在說我嗎？
No.
哦，不。
I mean, obviously we wanna see you take your clothes off.
我是說，我們顯然是要看你跳脫衣舞的，
You big piece of eye candy.
你這個萬人迷。
Okay. Okay, ladies, can I have your attention, please?
好的，女士們，請注意了。
Oh, yeah.
哦！！
Did someone call for the long arm of the law?
有人呼喚法律的巨擘了嗎？
I should warn you, I have a concealed weapon.
我要警告你，我有秘密武器呦。
I hope you're familiar with this state's penal code.
我希望你們熟悉本州法律規則。
Okay, okay. Enough teasing.
好了好了，玩笑開夠了
Now for some pleasing.
現在該樂一樂了。
She cringed.
喔，她躲著我。
This is how I look when I'm turned-on.
這就是我興奮時候的樣子。
You were talking about me before.
你們剛才就是在說我。
Look, I don't need this. I'm out of here. Where's my hat?
我可不需要這些。 我要走了，我的帽子呢？
Look, I've been in this business for a long time.
我幹這行已經很長時間了。
Shocking.
駭人聽聞。
Now, if you'll just pay me my $300, I'll be on my way.
現在，你付我300塊，我這就走人。
-$300? Are you kidding? -That's okay. Let me get my checkbook.
-300？你開什麼玩笑？ -沒關係，我來拿支票。
You're not gonna pay him. He didn't do anything.
不，你不用付他錢，他什麼也沒幹。
Didn't do anything? I took a bus all the way from Hoboken.
什麼也沒幹？ 我大老遠的從Holbolken搭公交車趕來
I climbed, I don't know, like, a billion stairs.
我爬了，天知道的，上億的台階。
And it's not like I can take them two at a time.
這可不像是我平時的消遣。
I don't care. We're not paying you $300 for this.
我不管，我們才不會就為這個付給你300塊錢。
It's not my fault if you're too uptight to appreciate..
那好，你那麼保守 欣賞不了男性的身材和魅力
the male form in all its glory.
這又不是我的錯。
Okay, I'm uptight. That's why I don't wanna watch a middle-aged guy..
哦，是，我保守，對 所以我不想看個半大老頭兒...
dance around in what I can only assume is a child's Halloween costume.
穿一身 我敢說是小孩萬聖節的行頭跳脫衣舞。
I may have borrowed this from my nephew..
我也許是從我侄子那兒借的衣服
but let me assure you, what's underneath is all man.
但我擔保衣服裡頭可是貨真價實的真男人。
I'm sorry, did you say "all man" or "old man"?
哦，抱歉，你是說真男人還是老男人？
You're mean.
哦，你可真刻薄。
-Look, officer.. Sir? -Damn it.
-哦，瞧，警官… -哦，該死，啊！
Big surprise. The hunk of beef has feelings.
沒想到吧，大胖子也很脆弱。
Applause.
鼓掌。
Okay, Henrietta, you picked "Jack and Jill Went Up The Hill."
好，亨瑞達 你選了"Jack and Jill Went Up The Hill"。
My friend Rachel has a kid. I totally know nursery rhymes.
我朋友瑞秋有個小孩，我對兒歌很熟悉。
Joey, describe these things associated with the United States Congress.
喬伊，描述以下跟美國國會有關的事物。
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
限時20秒。
Ready? Go.
預備，開始。
Pass.
過
-The thing hanging in your throat. -Uvula.
-呃，你喉嚨後面掛著的小東西。 -懸雍垂(小舌頭)。
Then pass.
哦，那，過。
Okay. Henrietta, you didn't get all the points you needed..
好了，亨瑞達，你沒有得到所需的點數
so that means, Gene, you are going to the Winner's Circle to try for $10,000.
所以，那就意味著，Gene 你將進入決勝圈來贏取$10000
And you're gonna be going there with Joey Tribbiani.
而且你將與 喬伊-崔比阿尼 一起參賽。
Pass.
過
Nope. You must be thinking of someone else.
不行, 你要為別人著想
I was never in a band.
我從來沒加入過樂隊
You made out with Missy Goldberg?
你跟米西.戈爾伯格親熱過？
How could you do that after you promised me?
你怎麼能在向我保證過之後還這麼做？
Excuse me.
失陪一下。
That didn't make us sound gay at all.
那聽起來倒一點不像同性戀。
-You broke the pact. -Ross, that was 16 years ago.
-你違反了君子協定。 -羅斯，那是16年前的事了。
That doesn't matter. We're talking about the foundation of our friendship.
那也不行，現在說的是我們之間友誼的基礎。
I believe the foundation of our friendship was unfortunate hair.
我以為我們之間友誼的基礎是難堪的髮型。
If we're really gonna do this, it's not like you never broke one of the pacts.
好吧，你看，要是我們真的明算賬的話， 你也不是沒幹過違反君子協定的事。
-I didn't. -Oh, really?
-我沒有。 -真的？
-No. -Oh, really?
-沒有。 -真的？！
-No. -Adrienne Turner.
-沒有。 -安卓.特娜
Yes?
在.
-Hey, Adrienne. -Hey, Adrienne. Hey.
-嘿, 安卓 -嘿, 安卓. 嘿
I never did anything with Adrienne Turner.
我從沒跟安卓.特娜攪和到一起。
Oh, please. And you knew how much I liked her.
哦，得了吧，你知道我有多喜歡他。
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在說什麼。
Really? Remember that party freshman year?
真的？還記得那個入學後第一個聖誕節假期 前一周的晚會嗎？
A week before Christmas vacation? I do.
前一周的晚會嗎？
You had some visitors.
我記得，當時有人找你。
I can't believe we're at a real college party.
難以置信我們在一個真的大學聚會上。
I have to pee so bad.
我興奮的直想尿尿。
This is so awesome.
這可真棒。
College guys are so cute.
大學男生好可愛。
-Hey, you've got a boyfriend. -I know.
-嘿，你有男朋友了。 -我知道
But if a guy who looks like Corey Haim wants to kiss me, I am so gonna let him.
不過要是有個像克瑞.哈姆那樣的想親我 我是不會拒絕的。
Hey, look, there's Chandler.
嘿，那是錢德。
That stupid friend of Ross' who said I was fat.
你知道的，羅斯的傻朋友，說我胖的那個。
-I've already lost four pounds. -You can so totally tell.
-你要知道，我都瘦掉4磅了。 -就是，一眼就看得出來。
I know!
我就知道！
Well, let's see, maybe he knows where Ross is.
問問他羅斯在哪。
Hey, how's it going?
嘿，怎麼樣？
-Aren't you..? -Yeah, Rachel.
-你不是… -對，瑞秋。
And this is Ross' sister, Monica. We met at Thanksgiving.
這是羅斯的妹妹，莫妮卡。 我們感恩節見過。
Right. So how you doing?
對。那，您怎麼樣？
Bitchen.
更浪了。
-Hi, Monica. -Hi, Chandler.
-嗨，莫妮卡。 -嗨，錢德。
It's really nice to see you. Not!
我是說，見到你很高興...才怪。
Okay.
好吧。
I'll see if I can find Ross.
我看看能不能找到羅斯。
Oh, my God, Rach. Beanbag chairs.
哦, 我的天，瑞秋，充氣椅。
Do not let me sit in one of those. We'll be here for days.
千萬別讓我坐上去，不然我們就走不了了。
Listen, Adrienne, you can't tell Chandler about this.
聽著，安卓，你可不能告訴錢德。
Oh, believe me, Ross, I won't be telling anybody about this.
哦，相信我，羅斯，我不會告訴任何人的。
Cool.
酷。
No way.
不可能
I didn't know you knew about that.
我以為你不知道。
Well, I did. And it hurt.
但是我知道了，我還很傷心。
That's when I wrote the song "Betrayal in the Common Room."
所以我才寫了"在休息室被背叛"那首歌。
That's why that song had so much power.
所以那首歌才那麼帶勁
Man, I'm sorry.
嘿，對不起。
Look, that was a long time ago.
好了，那都是陳年往事了。
So I made out with Adrienne, and you made out with Missy.
那，我跟安卓親熱，而你跟米西親熱。
Well, I guess we're even.
我看我們倆扯平了。
We are even, right?
我們倆扯平了，對吧？
One more thing. I was so pissed at you that night, I wanted to get back at you.
還有一件事。 那晚我特生你的氣，想報復你
So I thought, "Who does Ross like more than anybody?"
所以我當時想，誰是羅斯最喜歡的人呢。
What did you do to my mom?
你對我媽做了什麼？
Not her.
不是她。
I am so drunk.
我可真醉了。
That's weird. I've had the same number of beers as you and don't feel anything.
那就怪了，我跟你喝的差不多 怎麼我一點事兒沒有。
So you girls having fun?
你們倆玩的好嗎？
For your information, ass-munch..
跟你說，好的不得了。
I've lost four pounds. Maybe even five with all the dancing.
我瘦了4磅，沒準兒跳完舞會瘦5磅。
-Somebody order a pizza? -Oh, that's me!
-有人定比薩餅了嗎？ -哦，是我。
I am so not gonna do good on my SATs tomorrow.
我明天的入學考試算是沒戲了。
Well, maybe you could go to school here next year and we could totally hang out.
那，明年也許你可以到我們這兒來上大學 我們可以一塊玩玩。
Oh, yeah. There's a plan.
哦，對，你說得挺輕鬆，
Why don't I just start taking my smart pills now.
那我乾脆現在就吃點腦靈通得了。
Well, maybe you could get in on a beauty scholarship.
唔，沒準兒你能拿到選美獎學金呢。
What a line.
哦，別騙人了
-So where are you applying to? -Well..
-那，你都申請了哪些學校？ -唔..
I think it's kind of really important that I go somewhere where there's sun.
你知道，我覺著我要去的地方應該陽光明媚 這很重要，所以我想…
So I'm sort of.. Hey!
所以我想…嗨！
I'm in college, and I'm in a band.
我是大學生，還是樂隊成員。
Yeah, okay.
那好吧。
What's the matter? You never saw a 50-year-old stripper cry before?
怎麼啦，你們沒見過五十歲的脫衣舞男哭過嗎？
You know, it's fine. We'll pay you.
你看，算了吧，我們付你錢還不行嗎。
No, no, you're right. Who am I kidding?
不是那麼回事兒，你說的對，我在開誰的玩笑？
I should have hung up that breakaway jockstrap years ago.
早幾年我就該用那條脫開的護身帶上吊算了。
Half the time, it just pops off by itself.
經常的它自己就斷開了
Maybe now is a good time for cake and presents.
也許現在應該是蛋糕和禮物的時間
What am I gonna do? I mean..
現在我該怎麼辦？
this has been my life for 32 years.
我是說，我幹這個都32年了。
Taking my clothes off in front of people is all I know.
我只會在人家面前脫衣服。
No, there's got to be something else that you can do.
哦，等等，一定還有別的事你能做的。
I mean, what skills do you have?
我是說，你還有什麼技術嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I can make my pecs dance.
我能跳肚皮舞。
I can pick up a dollar bill with my butt cheeks.
我可以用屁股蛋兒夾起1美元的鈔票。
I can go to that special place inside me where I feel no shame.
我能變得毫無廉恥之心。
So maybe something in an office.
那你也許可以從政。
Or you could.. You could teach stripping.
或者你可以教人跳脫衣舞。
You know, share your gift. Pass the torch.
你知道嗎？分享你的才能，發揚光大。
You know, actually, that's not a bad idea.
對呀，這主意不賴
I could do it out of my apartment. I don't think my mom would mind.
我可以在我的公寓外頭干。 我想我媽不會介意的。
There you go. Okay. You think you're gonna be okay?
這下好啦，你感覺好一點了吧？
-Yeah. Yeah. -Yeah.
-對，好點了 -好
This is so weird.
世事難料啊。
You never know when it's gonna be your last dance.
你不會知道什麼時候曲終人散。
And I didn't even get a chance to finish it.
而且我甚至都沒能跳完最後一支舞。
Finish it.
那你把它跳完吧。
-What? -Your last dance. Do it for us.
-什麼？ -你的最後一次，給我們跳完吧。
-Really? -Really?
-你當真？ -你當真？
Yeah. Yeah, he deserves to do the thing he loves one last time.
是的，他應該最後再做一次他喜愛的事。
Okay. All right. Get ready, ladies.
好的，準備好了，女士們。
Okay.
好了
Oh, this is so hot!
哦，這可真讓人興奮！
Oh, no, don't stop.
哦，別，別停下來。
Have to.
跳不動了。
I am so sorry that you have to do this with me.
真抱歉你要和我一起幹這個
Listen, I know this won't put your kid through college..
聽著, 我知道這個不能送你的孩子去大學..
but would you like a Days of our Lives mug?
但是, 你喜歡《Days of our Lives》的杯子嗎
We're back in five, four, three, two..
我們現在倒數5,4,3,2..
Applause.
鼓掌
Welcome to the Winner's Circle. Joey, Gene, you guys ready?
歡迎來到決勝圈。 喬伊，金，你們準備好了嗎？
-Yeah. -Sure.
-好了。 -當然。
Okay. Give me 60 seconds on the clock, please.
好，限時60秒。
Ready? Go.
預備，開始。
Oak. Maple. Elm. Birch.
橡樹，楓樹，榆樹，樺樹…
I don't know. Types of trees..?
我-我-我不知道，樹種？
Buenos dias. Enchilada. Por favor.
(西班牙語)
Oh, I'm so sorry, I don't know any Spanish words.
哦，抱歉，我一點不懂西班牙語。
A match. A candle.
火柴，蠟燭…
Things that go: when you put them out.
撲滅時發出"滋"聲的東西。
A torch. A bonfire.
火炬，篝火…
-Your pee. -Things that burn.
-哦，你的小便。 -燃燒物。
"I'd like to go for a walk." "Scratch my belly."
我要去散散步。 撓撓我的肚皮。
Dude. Dude, I think you're losing it.
哥們兒，我覺得你說的太亂了。
"I have fur." "I like to bark."
呃，我有毛，我會吠叫。
What a dog says.
哦，這狗說的好啊
-Pepperoni. -Pizza toppings!
-意大利辣香腸… -比薩餅料。下一個！
Cindy Crawford. Christie Brinkley. Heidi Klum.
辛迪.克勞馥，克莉斯蒂.布林克利 海蒂.克勞姆，克勞迪婭.西佛。
Claudia Schiffer. Christy Turlington. Kate Moss.
克莉斯蒂.特林頓，凱特.瑪斯…
Girls Chandler could never get?
錢德永遠追不上的姑娘。
-Supermodels. -Where?
-超級名模！ -哪兒？！
I can't believe you're so upset.
真沒想到你這麼生氣
What do you mean? You kissed Rachel.
-你說呢?你吻了瑞秋
Ross, she was so drunk she didn't even remember it the next day.
羅斯, 她喝太多了 她第二天甚至什麼也不記得了
Plus, I should tell you, it did not last long.
另外我要告訴你, 那個並沒持續太長
Hey!
嘿!
I'm in college, and I'm in a band.
我上大學, 而且在玩音樂
Yeah, okay.
啊, 好啊!
And now I've killed one.
而且我已經搞定了一個
Hey. Where's Rachel?
嘿，瑞秋在哪？
She and Phoebe took the stripper to the hospital.
她和菲比送脫衣舞男上醫院了。
Sounds like your elegant tea party went off just as planned.
聽起來好像你的"一流茶會"按計劃進行
Did you know Chandler kissed Rachel?
你知不知道錢德吻過瑞秋？
What? When was this?
什麼？什麼時候？
Last week. We had some wine and..
上周, 我們喝了些酒, 然後..
You don't know I'm kidding.
你不知道我是開玩笑的
1987.
1987年。
The weekend you guys visited me at school.
你們倆上學校找我去的那個週末。
-Oh, my God. That's wild. -But it was, like, a million years ago.
-我的天，那也太放肆了。 -是，不過那是很久以前的事了
-It doesn't matter. -It matters to me.
-沒什麼要緊的。 -但那對我很要緊。
-Why? -Because the night you kissed Rachel..
-為什麼？ -因為你吻瑞秋的那晚
was the night I kissed Rachel for the very first time.
是我第一次吻瑞秋。
-You kissed her that night too? -Two guys in one night?
-你那晚也吻瑞秋了？ -一晚上兩個男人？
Oh, I thought she became a slut after she got her nose fixed.
我還以為她整過鼻子以後才變得放蕩了呢。
-Seriously, where did this happen? -Okay..
-真的，你在哪兒吻的瑞秋？ -是這樣的
after you told me she was passed out in our room..
你告訴我瑞秋在我們屋裡睡了之後
I went in there to make sure she was all right.
我進去看看她怎麼樣了。
She was lying on my bed, all buried in people's coats.
她躺在我床上，睡在一堆衣服下面。
I went to kiss her on the forehead..
呃，我過去想吻她的額頭
but it was so dark, I accidentally got her lips.
但屋裡太暗，我不小心親到了她的嘴唇
I started to pull away, but then I felt her start to kiss me back.
我想回身但我覺得她也開始吻我。
It was only for a second, but it was amazing.
那只有一瞬間但感覺太奇妙了。
And now I find out that you kissed her first.
但是現在，我卻發現你先吻了她。
-Wait, what bed did you say she was on? -Mine.
-呃，等等，你剛才說她在哪張床上？ -我床上。
-I'm sure I put her on my bed. -No, she was definitely on my bed.
-我記得很清楚我把她放到我床上的。 -不對，她肯定是在我床上。
Why would I kiss a girl and then put her on your bed?
我幹嗎吻完一個姑娘後把她放到你床上？
Well, then who was on my bed?
那當時我床上的是誰？
No! No!
哦，哦，哦！不！不！
Yes!
是的！
-You were under the pile of coats? -I was the pile of coats!
-你在那堆衣服下面？ -那堆衣服就是我。
Oh, my God!
哦，我的上帝！
You were my midnight mystery kisser?!
你是我的午夜神秘接吻人？
You were my first kiss with Rachel?!
你是我和瑞秋的初吻？
You were my first kiss ever?!
你就是我這輩子的初吻？！
What did I marry into?!
瞧瞧我結的什麼親家。
Crap!
哦，倒霉！